gearslutz.com 2016-12-01

# Gearslutz Pro Audio Community - FAQ: Site FAQ

**Privacy Policy**

Protecting your privacy is very important to Gearslutz.com. We have established this Privacy Policy which explains what information we collect from our visitors, how we use that information, and how you can view or control the use of the information you submit. Please note that this policy may be revised from time to time without notice, so please check it frequently. The current version of this policy is effective from 6 February 2014. 

Gearslutz.com asks for Personal Information only when we need information that personally identifies you ("Personal Information"). For example, we ask for your email address and obtain your location and your IP address when you register. We may collect additional information for contests, surveys or other promotions sponsored by Gearslutz.com and/or its promotional partners. We use your Personal Information to operate Gearslutz.com’s services, to help identify you and gather broad demographic information.

**Cookies**

Gearslutz.com and its advertisers place "cookies" in the browser files of your computer. Cookies are small pieces of information or files that are stored on a user's computer by web servers through a user's browser for record keeping purposes. The information can be retrieved to personalise, monitor, or regulate use of the site. Cookies allow Gearslutz.com to automate access and data entry functions of the site, such as login information, and tailor the site to a user's preferences, settings or interests. In addition, cookies allow Gearslutz.com to track usage of the site to determine those areas of the site that are useful or popular (and those that are not), thereby enabling Gearslutz.com to improve and update its service. You may remove these cookies at any time with your browser’s ‘Delete [or ‘Clear’] Cookies’ function, but your ability to use the site may be hampered by doing so.

Click on the link below to find out exactly what ‘cookies’ we use.

<https://www.gearslutz.com/board/cookies.php>

**Direct Mailings and "Opting Out"**

When you register for membership on Gearslutz.com you grant us permission to send site-related communications to you via email. You may opt-out of these communications at any time via the settings in your User CP or via the ‘unsubscribe’ links in emails we send you. 

**Public Forums**

Gearslutz.com offers “user provided” content. Users should be aware that when they voluntarily disclose Personal Information to other users or third parties on Gearslutz.com, via Private Messaging, or through email, or outside of Gearslutz.com, that information can be collected and used by others and may result in unsolicited messages from other members or parties. While Gearslutz.com strives to protect your Personal Information, Gearslutz.com cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to Gearslutz.com. 

You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of passwords and other account information.

**Links to Other Websites**

Gearslutz.com may provide links to its partners and other non-affiliated Internet websites. These sites have separate data and privacy practices independent of Gearslutz.com and Gearslutz.com disclaims any and all responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.

**Correcting and Updating Your Information**

You can view and make changes to the information you have previously provided to Gearslutz.com by visiting your online Profile (User CP). To delete your account, please contact support@gearslutz.com.

**Security**

To protect the security of your Personal Information, Gearslutz.com limits access to user data to authorised Gearslutz.com personnel. Gearslutz.com will NOT disclose any Personal Information except as described above or in our Terms & Conditions. Gearslutz.com may disclose user information, including demographic data, in an aggregated form that does not identify individual users in order to describe its services to prospective partners, advertisers and other third parties and for other lawful purposes. Gearslutz.com may disclose information about you if we have a good faith belief that we are required to do so by law or legal process, to respond to claims, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Gearslutz.com.

**Data Protection Act 1988 (UK/EU)**

If you are a resident of the EU/UK then you may request details of the Personal Information we have collected from you under the relevant Data Protection Legislation. If you would like a copy of the information we have collected from you when using the Website please write to Gearslutz.com LTD, Suite 201 Berkshire House, 39-51 High Street, Ascot SL5 7HY, UK. Please enclose a postal money order for £10.00 (UK/Sterling, payable to Gearslutz.com LTD) to cover processing costs.

**CalOPPA Compliance Statement (California 2014 Privacy Law)**

Gearslutz.com allows third-party ‘tracking’ via ‘cookies’ across our site. These may be set via social networking plugins, search engine use, or via advertising banners. Please see above for details on how we use cookies.

Gearslutz.com treats all ‘do not track’ requests from browser plugins/add-ons without prejudice, but it is impossible for us to offer our services without collecting data as described above and thus cannot offer ‘opt-out’ on a ‘manual’ or ‘case by case' basis.

If you are a resident of the State of California (USA) and you do not consent to this data collection/third party cookie placement under the California 2014 Privacy Law, please do not use Gearslutz.com.

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, or if you believe Gearslutz.com has not adhered to these principles, please contact us at support@gearslutz.com.
